share-games.com 2019-08-13

# Share-Games: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy :

share-games.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. 

**Electronic Newsletters** share-games.com is the partner of the BigFishGames.com . BigFishGames.com offers free electronic newsletters to users. share-games.com gathers the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Customers may receive BigFishGames.com newsletters periodically, customers can remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained in every newsletter. They can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration. 

**Surveys** share-games.com occasionally conducts customer surveys to better target our content and product inventory to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously. 

**Contests and sweepstakes** share-games.com offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. Information gathered is used only to verify user identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients, except when specifically noted otherwise. Again, we do not share information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously. 

**Usage tracking** share-games.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout share-games.com and this information is correlated with data about individual users. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type gotten by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser), are also broken down. share-games.com also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. 

**Cookies** A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such including a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. share-games.com uses cookies to track the items you add to your shopping card and to enforce security rules regarding software that you download. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, you need to have cookies turned on to purchase software through share-games.com. And We may use cookies to identify your location in order to provide you with better and more personalized services. 

**Unsubscribe Policy** Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter.
